See it with a song in your heart!
Listen, Darling is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Edwin L. Marin.
To stop Pinkie's widowed, struggling mother Dottie from marrying a well-off older man they know she doesn't love, teenager
Pinkie and her best friend Buzz kidnap her in the family travel trailer to live a carefree life on the open road.
They then get the idea to find Dottie a financially secure
husband whom both she and Pinkie would like.
Pinkie Wingate, played by Judy Garland.
Buzz Mitchell, played by Freddie Bartholomew.
Dottie Wingate, played by Mary Astor.
Richard Thurlow, played by Walter Pidgeon.
J.J. Slattery, played by Alan Hale.
Billie Wingate, played by Scotty Beckett.
Listen, Darling is a 1938 American musical comedy film starring Judy
Garland, Freddie Bartholomew, Mary Astor, and Walter Pidgeon.
It is best known as being the film in which Judy Garland sings "Zing!
Went the Strings of My Heart", which later became one of her standards.
The film explores themes of parent child relationship, widow,
campsite, road trip, marriage of convenience.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.